{
    "subject": "resource/Nusrat_Fateh_Ali_Khan",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1948-10-13",
    "human_readable": "Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on October 13, 1948.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9833362102508545,
            "question": "Is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's birthdate October 13th?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9438298940658569,
            "question": "When was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8870421051979065,
            "question": "Who was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.867188572883606,
            "question": "In what country was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6915627717971802,
            "question": "What is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5883672833442688,
            "question": "Was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan a popular musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5849462151527405,
            "question": "What year did Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5581067800521851,
            "question": "What is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3895760476589203,
            "question": "What musical genre is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3812619149684906,
            "question": "How influential was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan in the music world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on October 13, 1948.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1972_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical genre is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1972_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's legacy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1972_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1972_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1972_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information and without prior knowledge, I will evaluate whether the statement \"Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on October 13, 1948\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere's my evaluation:\n\n* The documents mention Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's birthdate as:\n\t+ Oct. 13, 1948 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1972/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt)\n\t+ October 13, 1948 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1972/re-ranker-msmarco/92.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1972/re-ranker-msmarco/59.txt)\n\t+ 13th October, 1948 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1972/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1972/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt)\n\nAll the documents consistently mention that Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on October 13, 1948. Therefore:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided consistently state that Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on October 13, 1948. Therefore, the statement \"Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on October 13, 1948\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}